<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Shayan's Blog</title><link>https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/</link><description>Recent content on Shayan's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.139.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 20:04:46 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starting A New Series</title><link>https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/posts/starting-anew-series/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 20:04:46 +0330</pubDate><guid>https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/posts/starting-anew-series/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="writing-is-fun">Writing is fun&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Hello everyone, Welcome to my first blog post (technically I&amp;rsquo;m wrong but anyways).
The other day, I was just trying doom Emacs and fell in love with it (I have been using neovim for 2 years now) specially the org-mode feature which is way better than any other task management system that i have used since i started using them (near 3 years). I&amp;rsquo;ll probably write about this in another post. As you can probably guess from the header, I have finally found a way that I can share my thoughts easily. Writing, yes. You know, I love YouTube and I believe that it&amp;rsquo;s the superior platform, but The thing is that whenever I tried to make YouTube video, I&amp;rsquo;ll just write very long script read of off it. Which brings me to this conclusion,&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>You Gotta Ask People</title><link>https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/posts/you-gotta-ask-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 01:08:59 +0330</pubDate><guid>https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/posts/you-gotta-ask-people/</guid><description>&lt;p>As Steve Jobs said you ask people for help or anything
He says that in experience people don&amp;rsquo;t usually refuse your request.
But you know let&amp;rsquo;s imagine there&amp;rsquo;s a 1/1000 chance of someone answering you email. That means if you email 1000 people you gotta get at least one answer and that&amp;rsquo;s a pretty good reason for me to start emailing people and containg people that I like.
&lt;img alt="My man steve" loading="lazy" src="https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/images/steve-jobs.jpg">&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why Nothing Is Fair in School</title><link>https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/posts/why-nothing-is-fair-in-school/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 01:03:53 +0330</pubDate><guid>https://shayan15sa.github.io/shayan-blog/posts/why-nothing-is-fair-in-school/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="intro">Intro&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>hey, have you ever you think why if student arrived late would get punished but teachers not.
look at least in most of the schools in Iran, WE ARE paying a lot of money to the schools so, why are we not paying attention to it or are we ok with that?&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="main">Main&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="we-are-paying-money">WE ARE PAYING MONEY&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>yes that&amp;rsquo;s our money which is wasted every single second that teachers are late so we&amp;rsquo;d better fight for our rights.
Imagine you pay someone hour by hour for watching your windows if you see him talking to the phone for half an hour right in middle of washing what do you do?
that&amp;rsquo;s easy you just fire him or you tell him not to do that right?
It is the exact same deal for the school. you are paying the teachers to drink tea.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>